var dataBank = [

	{	
		index: 0,
		question : "Javascript is a ______ language",
		answer: ['Programming', "Application", "Scripting", "None of the above"],
		rightAnsIndex: 2,
		qaURL: ""
	},

	{	
		index: 1,
		question : "Javascript is a ______ language",
		answer: ['Compiled', "Interpreted", "Both", "None"],
		rightAnsIndex: 2,
		qaURL: ""
	}, 

	{	
		index: 2,
		question : "Integer Variable is declared using following syntax in JavaScript.",
		answer: ['Integer num;', "var num", "int num", "all the above"],
		rightAnsIndex: 2,
		qaURL: ""
	}, 

	{	
		index: 3,
		question : "var num; Is a ______ statement.",
		answer: ['Instantiation', "Declaration", "Globalization", "Initialization"],
		rightAnsIndex: 2,
		qaURL: ""
	}, 
	{
		index: 4,
		question : "Add and Assignment operator is shown by this symbol.",
		answer: ['+==', "+=", "=+", "==+"],
		rightAnsIndex: 2,
		qaURL: ""
	},
	{
		index: 5,
		question : "'===' operator is _______________.",
		answer: ['is equal to', "is equal to and same type", "is equal to and different type", "assignment"],
		rightAnsIndex: 2,
		qaURL: ""
	},
	{
		index: 6,
		question : "'+=' operator can operate on following data values.",
		answer: ['Float', "String", "Integer", "All the above"],
		rightAnsIndex: 4,
		qaURL: ""
	},
	{
		index: 7,
		question : "JavaScript Statements are executed by ________ .",
		answer: ['Server', "JVM", "Compiler", "Browser"],
		rightAnsIndex: 4,
		qaURL: ""
	},
	{
		index: 8,
		question : "Which of the following statement is used to declare variable in JavaScript ?",
		answer: ['Assignment', "Declaration", "Conditional", "Executable"],
		rightAnsIndex: 2,
		qaURL: ""
	},
	{
		index: 9,
		question : "Which built-in method returns the length of the string?",
		answer: ['length()', "index()", "size()", "All of the above"],
		rightAnsIndex: 1,
		qaURL: ""
	},
	{
		index: 10,
		question : "Which of the below is used in Java script to insert special characters?",
		answer: ['%', ' \ ', "&", "^"],
		rightAnsIndex: 1,
		qaURL: ""
	}
	// {
	// 	index: 11,
	// 	question : "var num; Is a ______ statement.",
	// 	answer: ['Instantiation', "Declaration", "Globalization", "Initialization"],
	// 	qaURL: ""
	// },
	// {
	// 	index: 12,
	// 	question : "var num; Is a ______ statement.",
	// 	answer: ['Instantiation', "Declaration", "Globalization", "Initialization"],
	// 	qaURL: ""
	// },
	// {
	// 	index: 13,
	// 	question : "var num; Is a ______ statement.",
	// 	answer: ['Instantiation', "Declaration", "Globalization", "Initialization"],
	// 	qaURL: ""
	// },
	// {
	// 	index: 14,
	// 	question : "var num; Is a ______ statement.",
	// 	answer: ['Instantiation', "Declaration", "Globalization", "Initialization"],
	// 	qaURL: ""
	// },
	// {
	// 	index: 15,
	// 	question : "var num; Is a ______ statement.",
	// 	answer: ['Instantiation', "Declaration", "Globalization", "Initialization"],
	// 	qaURL: ""
	// },
	// {
	// 	index: 16,
	// 	question : "var num; Is a ______ statement.",
	// 	answer: ['Instantiation', "Declaration", "Globalization", "Initialization"],
	// 	qaURL: ""
	// },
	// {
	// 	index: 17,
	// 	question : "var num; Is a ______ statement.",
	// 	answer: ['Instantiation', "Declaration", "Globalization", "Initialization"],
	// 	qaURL: ""
	// }
















];

